Finding Aid for Alumni Association (University of Michigan) records, 1845-2001
Bentley Historical Library
- Topical Files, 1847-1994; undated
  - Culver, Frank H. (re: Founding Date of University of Michigan), 1929 (Box 158)
  - Development Committee, 1955-1987
    - 1955-1968 (Box 164)
    - 1966-1987 (Box 164)
  - Development Relations Committee, 1981-1984 (Box 158)
  - Distinguished Alumni Service Award (includes historical listing), 1982-1986 (Box 158)
  - Education Information Programs, 1957 (Box 158)
  - Entrepreneur Academy of Grand Rapids, 1994 (Box 169)
  - Events Calendar, 1982-1985 (Box 158)
  - Faculty Advisory Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 158)
  - Field Secretary's Bulletin, 1927; 1962-1965 (Box 158)
  - Government Information Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 159)
  - Hadley, Frederick S. (1885) (Reminiscences re: Angell Administration), 1935 (Box 159)
  - Inteflex Alumni, 1982-1984 (Box 159)
  - Lawton, Fred (includes poetry), 1957-1969 (Box 159)
  - Lightner, F.W. (offer to sponsor a contest for a new college song or yell), 1909 (Box 159)
  - Medical Center Alumni Society (includes history of), 1975-1984 (Box 159)
  - Michigan Alumni Academy, 1966-1981 (Box 159)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 159)
    - Charter meeting minutes, 1966-1989 (Box 164)
    - Special Section (Nominating Committee, Pins/emblems/jewelry, Rosters, Trustees, 1966-1976 (Box 164)
  - Minority Recruitment Program, 1978-1993; undated
    - Minority Recruitment Proposal, undated (Box 159)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990-1992 (Box 169)
    - Native American Student Recruitment, 1978-1992 (with gaps); undated (Box 169)
    - Visiting Prospective Students, 1993 (Box 169)
  - Michigan Annual Giving Scholars, 1980-1993 (Box 159)
  - Moon Chapter (Michigan Alumni Apollo Space Mission), 1971 (Box 159)
  - Ninth District Alumni Association, Annual Conference, 1940-1941 (Box 159)
  - Omega Phi (Mrs. Carl Wagner letter re: women's debating society), 1954 (Box 159)
  - Organizations and Extension Committee, 1944-1954 (Box 159)
  - Physical Therapy Alumni Association, 1984 (Box 159)
  - Policy Committee, 1955-1987; 5 folders (Box 165)
  - Prominent Minority Alumni, undated (Box 169)
  - Public Affairs and Reunion Committee, 1944-1954 (Box 159)
  - Publications Committee, 1943-1987; 2 folders (Box 159)
  - Racism, 1987; undated
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 169)
    - Special Hearing and Testimony, 1987 (Box 169)
    - Racism and Minority Enrollment Panel Discussion: Michigan Alumnus, 1987 (Box 159)
    - Reports and Statements, 1987; undated (Box 169)
  - Regents Alumni Scholars Program, 1980-1993 (Box 159)
  - Reports, 1965; 1984
    - Anatomy of a District, 1965 (Box 159)
    - The University of Michigan's Alumni (draft), 1984 (Box 159)
  - Report to the President, Annual, 1983 (Box 159)
  - Second District Conference (minutes), 1960 (Box 159)
  - Sesquicentennial, 1966 (Box 159)
  - Study Committee Report, 1961 (Box 159)
  - Tappan Oak (and Class of 1858), 1944 (Box 159)
  - Tapping, Hawley (correspondence re: Philippines), 1960-1961 (Box 159)
  - U of M Clubs, 1959-1987
    - Buffalo, 1960-1962 (Box 159)
    - Chicago, 1959-1962 (Box 159)
    - Detroit, 1960-1962 (Box 159)
    - General, 1986-1987; 2 folders (Box 159)
      (includes executive members by city)
    - Michigan District Officers, 1986 (Box 159)
    - Miscellaneous, 1959-1961 (Box 159)
  - Waltz, Stanley G. Alumni Scholarship, 1993 (Box 159)
  - Wrentmore, Margaret (article about life in 1890s), circa 1943 (Box 159)
- Audio-Visual Materials, 1960-1994; undated
  The Audio-Visual Files (boxes 147; 149; 161-163; 169-171) include audio recordings of lectures from various University of Michigan faculty and staff on the sciences (including computer, environmental, library, and medical); as well as musical performances, and sporting events. Also included are color slides from the Michigan Alumnus magazine, and the Reunion of Black Graduates annual meetings. The series also contains color slides of the Honorable Geraldine Bledsoe Ford (the first African American woman in the United States to be elected to a judgeship).
  The videotapes within this series contain recordings-many by noteable U-M alumni, faculty, and staff on subjects including the history of Ann Arbor and U-M, science including the Human Genome Project, literacy, economics, politics, music, religion, art, civil rights, and education.
  - Audiotapes, 1960-1993; undated; (reel-to-reel, mostly 7 1/2 ips)
    [Digitized audio files are only available in the Bentley Historical Library reading room on designated Bentley Library computers.]
    The Audio Tapes series (Boxes 161-162) consists of reel-to-reel tape recordings of musical performances, dedications, interviews, and radio programs dating from 1960 to 1993. The tapes include performances by the Glee Club, Marching Band, and Amaizin' Blues. Sports-related tapes include two reels of "Football Report" from 1960 and 1961 containing interviews with former football coach and athletic director Fritz Crisler discussing substitution rules and other football topics. Equipment manager Henry Hatch also discusses changes in equipment and uniforms during his 42-year career. Other selections include a discussion of the Phoenix Memorial Project and atomic energy by professors Ralph Sawyer and Henry Gomberg.
    - "Magnetic Michigan", 1985-1993
      "Magnetic Michigan" consists of audiotapes and VHS videotapes featuring faculty members speaking on a variety of topics as part of the alumni continuing education program from 1985 to 1992. Faculty presenters include David Angus, Russell Bidlack, Nancy Cantor, James Chaffers, Francis Collins, Marion Marzolf, Harrison Morton, Michel Oksenberg, and Donn Werling. Topics include Michigan history, genetic research, Jens Jensen, Nichols Arboretum, school reform and urban planning. Several tapes include incomplete portions of lectures.
      - 1985-1992
        - "English Reputation of the University of Michigan, 1868-1969", W. H. G. Armytage (School of Education, University of Sheffield, England), 1987 February 26; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 162)
          - [Side 1], [8730-SR-18-1]; (Lecture entitled "English Reputation of the University of Michigan, 1868-1969" given by W. H. G. Armytage in the Founders Room Alumni Center on February, 26 1987 as part of the Celebration '87 Symposium Series -- "Heritage and Change: the University of Michigan in 1887, 1937, and 1987". Introductions by Robert G. Forman and Emeritas Professor Claude A. Eggertsen.)
          - [Side 2], [8730-SR-18-2]; (Continuation of lecture entitled "English Reputation of the University of Michigan, 1868-1969" given by W. H. G. Armytage in the Founders Room Alumni Center on February, 26 1987 as part of the Celebration '87 Symposium Series -- "Heritage and Change: the University of Michigan in 1887, 1937, and 1987". Introductions by Robert G. Forman and Emeritas Professor Claude A. Eggertsen.)
        - Lecture by Professor Jonathan Bulkley on Water Quality and Other Current Environmental Problems of the Great Lakes, 1987 November 17; Audio Cassette (Box 162)
          - [Side 1], [8730-SR-19-1]; (Lecture given by Professor Jonathan Bulkley on water quality and environmental issues of the Great Lakes on November 17, 1987 as part of Conversations with Faculty series.)
          - [Side 2], [8730-SR-19-2]; (Continuation of lecture given by Professor Jonathan Bulkley on water quality and environmental issues of the Great Lakes on November 17, 1987 as part of Conversations with Faculty series.)
        - Lecture by Professor Arthur Burks and Alice Burks on the ENIAC, the First Electronic Computer, 1988 April 26; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 162)
          - [Side 1], [8730-SR-20-1]; (Lecture given by Professor Arthur and Alice Burks on the ENIAC machine, the first electronic computer on April 26, 1988 as part of the Conversations with Faculty series. Side 1 of 3.)
          - [Side 2], [8730-SR-20-2]; (Continuation of lecture given by Professor Arthur and Alice Burks on the ENIAC machine, the first electronic computer on April 26, 1988 as part of the Conversations with Faculty series. Side 2 of 3.)
        - Lecture by Professor Arthur Burks and Alice Burks on the ENIAC, the First Electronic Computer, 1988 April 26; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 162)
          - [Side 1], [8730-SR-21-1]; (Continuation from previous tape of lecture given by Professor Arthur and Alice Burks on the ENIAC machine, the first electronic computer on April 26, 1988 as part of the Conversations with Faculty series. Side 3 of 3.)
          - [Side 2], [8730-SR-21-2]; (Continuation of lecture given by Professor Gordon MacAlpine about supernovae on July 6, 1988 as part of Conversations with Faculty series. Side 3 of 3.)
        - Lecture by Professor G. Michael Deeb, M.D. on the Current State of Heart Transplantation Surgery, 1987 April 21; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 162)
          - [Side 1], [8730-SR-22-1]; (Lecture given by Professor G. Michael Deeb, M.D. on the current state of heart transplantation surgery on April 21, 1987 as part of Conversations with Faculty series.)
          - [Side 2], [8730-SR-22-2]; (Continuation of lecture given by Professor G. Michael Deeb, M.D. on the current state of heart transplantation surgery on April 21, 1987 as part of Conversations with Faculty series.)
        - Lectures by Professors William Frey and Louis A. Ferman as part of "The Changing Face of America" enrichment series, 1986 June 21; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 162)
          - [Side 1], [8730-SR-23-1]; (Lectures given by Professor William H. Frey on immigration policies and statistics and Professor Louis A. Ferman on "The New Americans: the Challenge for Michigan", as part of "The Changing Face of America" enrichment series, June 21, 1986.)
          - [Side 2], [8730-SR-23-2]; (Continuation of lecture given by Professor Louis A. Ferman on "The New Americans: the Challenge for Michigan", as part of "The Changing Face of America" enrichment series on June 21, 1986. Includes question and answer session.)
        - Lecture by Michel Oksenberg on "Reflections on China Today" as part of Rose Bowl Faculty Seminar, 1988 December 31; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 162)
          - [Side 1], [8730-SR-24-1]; (Lecture entitled "Reflections on China Today" given by Professor Michel Oksenberg on December 31, 1988 in California as part of the Rose Bowl Faculty Seminar hosted by the University of Michigan Alumni Association.)
          - [Side 2], [8730-SR-24-2]; (Continuation of lecture entitled "Reflections on China Today" given by Professor Michel Oksenberg on December 31, 1988 in California as part of the Rose Bowl Faculty Seminar hosted by the University of Michigan Alumni Association. Recorded over another lecture by Professor Nancy Cantor. Oksenberg begins around 5:00 and ends around 39:00.)
        - Lectures by Professors Richard Teske and Roy Rappaport as part of Alumni Association Enrichment Series, 1986 March 25; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 162)
          - [Side 1], [8730-SR-25-1]; (Lecture given by Professor Richard Teske on Haley's Comet as part of Alumni Association Enrichment series on March 25, 1986.)
          - [Side 2], [8730-SR-25-2]; (Lecture given by Professor Roy Rappaport about the history and culture of Tahiti as part of Alumni Association Enrichment series on March 25, 1986.)
        - Lecture by Professor Martha Vicinus, "Kipling: His Age and Ours", 1986 March 22; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 162)
          - [Side 1], [8730-SR-26-1]; (Lecture given by Professor Martha Vicinus entitled, "Kipling: His Age and Ours" hosted by the University of Michigan Alumni Association on March 22, 1986.)
          - [Side 2], [8730-SR-26-2]; (Continuation of lecture given by Professor Martha Vicinus entitled, "Kipling: His Age and Ours" hosted by the University of Michigan Alumni Association on March 22, 1986.)
        - Lecture by Dean Robert M. Warner, School of Library Science, "Preserving Our Nation's Heritage", 1985 November 20; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 162)
          - [Side 1], [8730-SR-27-1]; (Lecture by Professor Robert M. Warner, Dean of the School of Library Science and former Archivist of the United States, entitled, "Preserving Our Nation's Heritage" given on November 20, 1985. Part of the Conversations with Faculty series hosted by the University of Michigan Alumni Association. Side 1 of 3.)
          - [Side 2], [8730-SR-27-2]; (Continuation of lecture by Professor Robert M. Warner, Dean of the School of Library Science and former Archivist of the United States, entitled, "Preserving Our Nation's Heritage" given on November 20, 1985. Part of the Conversations with Faculty series hosted by the University of Michigan Alumni Association. Side 2 of 3.)
        - Lectures by Dean Robert M. Warner and Professor Judith Elkin, 1992 August 24; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 162)
          - [Side 1], [8730-SR-28-1]; (Continuation of lecture given by Professor Judith Elkins on Jews in Hispanic Societies. Side 3 of 3, side 1-2 missing.)
          - [Side 2], [8730-SR-28-2]; (Continuation of lecture by Professor Robert M. Warner, Dean of the School of Library Science and former Archivist of the United States, entitled, "Preserving Our Nation's Heritage" given on November 20, 1985. Part of the Conversations with Faculty series hosted by the University of Michigan Alumni Association. Side 3 of 3.)
      - Catalog of Tapes Available, 1993
    - Miscellaneous, 1960; 1982; undated
      - Alumni Center Dedication, 1982; 3 3/4 ips (Box 161)
      - Background - Atomic Energy, (Ralph Sawyer and Henry Gomberg discuss the Phoenix Memorial Project), [Undated]; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch (Box 161)
        - [Part 1], [8730-SR-12-1-1]; (Interview with members of the Memorial Phoenix Project about atomic energy use.)
      - Little Brown Jug, a True Story, [Undated], 1982 November 1; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 161)
        - [Part 1], [8730-SR-13-1-1]; ("The True Story of the Little Brown Jug" as told by Tommy Roberts, student manager of the 1903 team who bought the original jug..)
        - [Part 2], [8730-SR-13-1-2]; mp3 file; (Alumni Association Leadership Conference Tape 3; Alumni Association Conference. University President Shapiro speaks. (Tape 2 of confernece recorded on "Henry Hatch" reel, 8730-SR-11-1-1-2)
      - Men of Science and Osborn Documentary, [Undated], 1960; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 161)
        - [Part 1], [8730-SR-14-1-1]; (Interview with Don Glaser, Nobel prize-winner - before being awarded the prize and documentary program about Chase S. Osborn. (The Osborn Documentary is also on a separate tape as part of the WUOM "Michigan Week" progam, May 1960, under the title "Tribute to Chase Osborn."))
      - "One Nation Indivisible" --award winning documentary on Nationalism in the 20th century, WUOM, [Undated]; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 161)
        - [Part 1], [8730-SR-15-1-1]; ("One Nation Indivisible" is a series of radio documents telling the story of eleven countries or areas of the world which are deeply stirred by nationalistic feelings and aspirations. The programs have been produced in consultation with University of Michigan faculty specialists. Foreign students studying at the University appear as narrators throughout the series.)
      - Tour of Campus, pre, 1982 (Box 161)
        (from a presentation to the Alumni)
    - Musical Performances, 1960-1977; undated
      - Amaizin' Blues; First Annual Campus Concert; John A. Smith, artistic director, 1976 March 28; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 161)
        - [Tape 1, Part 1], [8730-SR-1-1-1]; (Tape 1 of 2; Amaizin' Blues performs first concert, part 1. Performs Magic to Do, I Dig Rock and Roll Music, Happy Together, Corner of the Sky, Walk Softly, Alexander's Ragtime Band, Pieces of Dreams, Look for the Beauty, Sunshine in My Soul, You're the Top, Temptation, Won't Someone Please Speak Kindly to the Tenor; Coney Island Baby, Godspell (Choral Selections).)
        - [Tape 2, Part 1], [8730-SR-1-2-1]; (Tape 2 of 2; Amaizin' Blues performs first concert, part 2. Pieces performed: Improvisation, Get Happy (a 30's montage), Touch the Wind, It Had to Be You, The Rhythm of Life, Burgers and Beer, Lonely Room, American Folk Trilogy, Varsity, College Days / I Want To Go Back to Michigan, If We Only Have Love.)
      - Amaizin' Blues at the Power Center, 1977 March 22; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 161)
        - [Part 1], [8730-SR-2-1-1]; (Part I: Amaizin' Blues performs Magic to Do, Alexander's Ragtime Band, Woodchoppers' Ball, Beautiful, Rhythm of Life, Soon It's Gonna Rain, Simple Joys, Big Spender, When I Fall In Love, Walk Him Up the Stairs, Send in the Clowns, College Days / I Want to Go Back to Michigan, Everybody Rejoice.)
        - [Part 2], [8730-SR-2-1-2]; mp3 file; (Part II: Amaizin' Blues performs I Hope I Get It, What I Did For Love, One, Chameleon, A Sentimental Journey Thru the 40's, If You Believe, Coney Island Baby, Varsity, If We Only Have, The Victors.)
      - Amaizin' Blues at the Power Center, 1977 November 18; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 161)
        - [Part 1], [8730-SR-3-1-1]; (Part II: Amaizin' Blues performs at the Power Center at 8:00 PM. Part I missing.)
      - Amaizin' Blues and The Wisconsin Collegiates, 1976 October 22; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 161)
        - [Tape 1, Part 1], [8730-SR-4-1-1]; (Tape 1 of 2; The Collegiates perform: Don't Take Away the Music, Stoney End, Opus One, Lady Madonna, Let There Be Love, What I Did For Love, Sing!, I Hope I Get It, Here's That Rainy Day, Celebrate, MacArthur Park, Land of Make Believe, Games People Play, Thank God I'm A Country Boy (not listed in Program), Dueling Banjos (not listed in Program), Crescent Moon, Goodbye Love, Bohemian Rhapsody. Song order is different than that of the program.)
        - [Tape 2, Part 1], [8730-SR-4-2-1]; (Tape 2 of 2; Amaizin' Blues performs Magic to Do, Alexander's Ragtime Band, Take Up the Hammer of Hope, This One's For You, Woodchopper's Ball, When I Fall in Love, Walk Him Up the Stairs, Nothing Can Stop Me Now, If, Everybody Rejoice, Maybe This Time, Burgers and Beer, Affirmation, Varsity, If We Only Have Love, The Victors.)
      - University of Michigan; Band Day, 1961; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 161)
        - [Part 1], [8730-SR-5-1-1]; (13,000 High School bandsmen perform 5 songs conducted by William Revelli and George Cavender, guest conductor Henry Walters; narrated by Ed Burroughs.)
      - The Hockettes, Live Music, [Undated]; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 161)
        - [Tape 1, Part 1], [8730-SR-6-1-1]; (Reel 1 of 2; Live music to accompany The Hockettes performances.)
        - [Tape 2, Part 1], [8730-SR-6-2-1]; (Reel 2 of 2; Live music to accompany The Hockettes performances.)
      - Men's Glee Club, live performance, performed for the Emeritus [Club] Induction Ceremony, 1980 May 01; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 161)
        - [Part 1], [8730-SR-7-1-1]; (The Men's Glee Club sing a selection of Michigan songs.)
      - University of Michigan Marching Band (Stars & Stripes Forever), 1960 October 08; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 161)
        - [Part 1], [8730-SR-8-1-1]; (UM Band Day Massed Bands performance of Stars & Stripes Forever.)
    - Sports, 1960-1961; undated
      - "Football Report"; Interviews with Jerry Smith, Bump Elliott, and Fritz Crisler, 1960-1961; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 161)
        - [Part 1], [8730-SR-9-1-1]; (Tape content does not match original description; Unknown speakers discussing University policies. A person identified as Mr. Wilson interviewed by officer of the Alumni Association. A debate on the subject of college attendance, particularly women at the university and University policies.)
        - [Part 2], [8730-SR-9-1-2]; mp3 file; (Interviews with Jerry Smith, team captain; Bump Elliott, head football coach, and Fritz Crisler.)
      - "Sports Report"; Fritz Crisler; Bennie Oosterban, 1961; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 161)
        - [Part 1], [8730-SR-10-1-1]; (Sports Report broadcast (5:00), Fritz Crisler discussing the new substitution rule in football (10:30), Bennie Oosterban interview (5:30).)
      - Henry Hatch, [Undated]; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 161)
        - [Tape 1, Part 1], [8730-SR-11-1-1-1]; (Henry Hatch, 42 year equipment manager, discusses how uniforms and equipment have changed during his tenure.)
        - [Tape 1, Part 2], [8730-SR-11-1-1-2]; (Alumni Association Leadership Conference Tape 2; Alumni Association Conference. University President Shapiro speaks.)
  - Slides, 1979-1990 (with gaps)
    - Michigan Alumnus Magazine (Box 147)
      (include individuals, Class of 1899, 1951 commencement, football rituals, and Ann Arbor views)
    - Reunion of Black Graduates, 1979-1990 (with gaps); 4 folders
      - 1979-1987 (with gaps), 4 folders (Box 169)
      - Honorable Geraldine Ford Bledsoe, 1998 (Box 169)
      - Workshow, 1990; 1 slide trays (Box 170)
  - Videotapes (VHS), 1988-1998
    - Achenbaum, W. Andrew
      - Can You Count on Getting Yours at 65? The New Politics of Aging, #71, 11/28/1989 (Box 162)
      - Kids vs. Canes: The New Politics of Aging, #246, 06/13/1994 (Box 162)
    - Angus, David L.
      - Grasping at Panaceas: School Reform in Michigan, #260, 07/12/1994 (Box 162)
    - Bailey, Richard W.
      - The Image of English, #151, 06/02/1992 (Box 162)
      - Nineteenth Century English, #205, 06/22/1993 (Box 162)
    - Berger, Carl F.
      - New Ways of Learning and Teaching: Evolution or Revolution, #213, 07/27/1993 (Box 162)
    - Bidlack, Russell E..
      - Andrew Ten Brook: A Forgotten Figure in U-M History, #84, 06/26/1990 (Box 162)
      - John Allen and the Founding of Ann Arbor, #44, 06/09/1989 (Box 162)
      - Genealogical Research: A Hobby for All Seasons, #7, (pt. 1, 06/26/1988 (Box 162)
      - Genealogical Research: A Hobby for All Seasons, #8, (pt. 2), 06/26/1988 (Box 162)
    - Blouin, Francis X., Jr.
      - The Bentley Library, the Vatican Archives, Archives in the New Russia: Improbable Collaborations, #211, 07/26/1993 (Box 162)
      - Michigan in the Era of Industrialization, #180, 08/11/1992 (Box 162)
    - Bulkey, Honathan W.
      - Pollution Prevention: A Concept Whose Time Has Come, #212, 07/27/1993 (Box 162)
    - Cantor, Nancy
      - Personality and Social Intelligence, #37, 11/29/1998 (Box 162)
    - Cavendar, George R.
      - So You Want to Run a Marching Band?. #68, 07/12/1989 (Box 162)
    - Chaffers, James
      - Urban Design and Social Change, #103, 8/28/1990 (Box 162)
    - Cohen, Carl
      - Ethical Issues Arising in the Care of Dying Patients, #1, 06/08/1988 (Box 162)
    - Cole, David E.
      - Automotive Industry in Transition: A Model for Change, #119, 06/19/1991 (Box 162)
    - Collins, Francis S.
      - The Human Genome Project and the Future of Medicine, #190, 11/24/1992 (Box 162)
    - Fader, Dan
      - Teaching Literacy at the University, #233, 11/10/1993 (Box 162)
    - Fine, John V. A.
      - The Crisis in Ex-Yugoslavia and Its Roots, #202, 06/21/1993 (Box 162)
      - Current Yugoslav Political, National, and Economic Problems in Their Historical Context, #77, 06/11/1990 (Box 162)
    - Fisk, Lennard A.
      - Space Research at The University of Michigan, #236., 04/04/1994 (Box 162)
    - Gere, Anne Ruggles
      - Perspectives on Literacy, #83, 06/25/1990 (Box 162)
    - Gilman, Sid
      - Alzheimer's Disease Research at Michigan, #237, 04/12/1994 (Box 162)
    - Glissman, Richard L., and Gail Rector